migvapor.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy Cookie Restriction Mode

WARNING: This product contains nicotine. Nicotine is an addictive chemical.

This Privacy Policy will give all the details about how we collect your personal information as well as how it could be used or shared when a purchase has been made with us.

## What Personal Information Do We Collect?

Any visitor to the site will have the details about the device automatically collected. This information includes the web browser, IP address, time zone, and specific cookies from your device.

We will collect data which indicates how you interacted with our site, such as web pages which were viewed, products which were viewed, what search terms were used to help land on our website, and data which helps us understand how you interacted with the site.

We define any of this information collected as "Device Data." This information can include referral and exit pages, time and date stamps, ISP, operating systems, etc.

## How Do We Collect This Data?

Most of the information available that gets transferred from your device to our site is collected by way of "Cookies." Cookies contain data stored on your device or computer that also includes usually anonymous, yet unique to you, identifiers. Read more about cookies [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

Log Files are also collected automatically which help us track your IP address, browser type, ISP. Also, these files contain the data which tell us about the referring pages, exit pages, and date and time stamps.

Electronic files sometimes referred to as beacons, pixels or tags are also tracked and record the information that helps us understand how you interacted with our site.

Any purchases will also enable us to collect information that includes your name, billing address, email, phone number and shipping address. Your payment information will consist of your credit card number. This data constitutes Order Information.

In some cases, a purchase will require a copy of a photo identification card and could be stored by the US Government.

Any Personal Information referred to in the Privacy Policy can include Order Information or Device Data.

## How is Your Personal Information Used?

Our use of your data is very straightforward. Once an order is fulfilled, we will need to send you the order confirmation to the email address provided, arrange shipping and process the payment.

Also, we may need to communicate with you to enhance the customer experience, to screen for any possible fraudulent activity, and, depending on user preference settings, advertise other related products or services that may interest you based on your

**Personal Information.**   
For us to detect any fraudulent activity, your IP address must be available to be collected. We also try to improve our customer user experience by using the analytics generated by tracking how our users interact with the site and gauging how successful our marketing campaigns have been.

## Is Your Personal Information Shared?

For us to understand how visitors use our site, we share data with Google Analytics. Visit the page [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) to read more about how Google uses your data. To opt out of your information being shared with Google, you can access the area to do that by visiting [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

To comply with local laws, we may be required to hand over Personal Information when presented with a subpoena. This is to protect ourselves and users of the site in case of any illegal activity, fraud or malicious breaches of the website security.

## Remarketing and Targeted Advertising

By using a pixel or other tracking software, advertisements are served based on browsing habits that may be of interest to you. By visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work, you can read up on how targeting advertising works.

In the event you would like to opt out of this type of targeted advertising, you can visit these relevant pages:

Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)

Google: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)

Bing: [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)

There is another opt-out service provided by the Digital Advertising Alliance on this page [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

## Do Not Track Signal

The Do Not Track software is a signal set in your browser that alerts sites like ours to request we not track your browsing habits. Be advised, that do not track signals do not alter the way we collect and use your Personal Information.

## Your Data Rights

If you are in Europe, then you have the right to access how your data is collected and has been used by our site. You have the right to request that this data be corrected, deleted or updated at any time. We have provided a customer service number in the event you would like to exercise this right, which can be found below.

The data we have collected is for the ability to fulfill a contract between you, a user of our site and us. Primarily for the matter of purchasing products through our website, or any other legal business practice. Some of this information will be passed along to servers outside Europe, primarily to the United States and Canada.

## Do We Retain Your Data?

Any data collected through a purchase from our website is held by us for our records unless specifically requested by you to delete this information.

## Is There an Age Restriction?

Users under the age of 21 are expressly prohibited from using our site or purchasing any products.

## Will This Policy Change?

In the event of any change in regulations, this policy will be updated and changed accordingly. It is the users' responsibility to check the Privacy Policy for any changes for this reason or any other operational or legal requirement.

For questions, complaints or to request access to your Personal Information that we have stored, please contact us by email at email@email.com, or by mail to (address to be provided).

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Our last Privacy Policy update was on October 23, 2018. Any future changes will be posted to this page and will include whatever updates to how Personal Information was collected and held after this date.

## Feedback

Any questions about your privacy that you may have are much appreciated and will be answered as soon as possible. 

## Terms and Conditions

Please visit the Terms and Conditions page to learn more about the use of this website along with any limits of our liability with regards to this use.

Also, note that the Privacy Policy is only applicable to any data gathered online and does not pertain to any information that may have been collected offline.
